lootmarket.com 2019-07-03

# Privacy Policy

## Purpose of the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy covers the lootmarket.com website (hereinafter “Website”), which is owned and operated by Loot Market, Inc. (“Loot Market”). Loot Market is committed to protecting the privacy of its users and wishes to maintain a safe and secure environment for all users of the Website. Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personal information is treated. From time to time, Loot Market may offer new services and/or products that may require Loot Market to update this Privacy Policy. Please check back with us periodically. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact Loot Market’s Privacy Administrator by email at help@lootmarket.com.

This Privacy Policy answers the following questions for you regarding your privacy protection:

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES LOOT MARKET COLLECT?

Loot Market collects personal information from users for different purposes.  Information gathered online can be identified as either anonymous or identifiable.  Anonymous information is information that cannot be traced back to the individual.  Identifiable information is information that is specific to an individual.

### Anonymous Information

Like many websites, the Website gathers certain information automatically and stores it.  This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, searches performed, browser types, Internet services providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, date/time stamps, and clickstream data. Loot Market uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, administer the Website, gather demographic information about its user base as a whole, and improve its level of service to you. Loot Market does not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

### Personally Identifiable Information

To use the Website, a user must register for an account. In order to create an account, a user must first have an account with Steam (www.steamcommunity.com) and possess a Steam username, password, and trade url. A user may then create an account on the Website by logging with his or her Steam account information. Loot Market will collect the following information from its users: (i) name, (ii) email address, (iii) financial data (credit card number, expiration date, cvv, billing zip code), and (iv) Steam username and/or Steam trade url. The provision of this personal information is mandatory and if you choose not to submit the requested information we will not be able to provide you with an account.

The Website may provide you with the opportunity to share content with another person. For such features to work, Loot Market may need to collect name and/or email address of the person with whom you want to share content. Loot Market does not store this information.

## DOES THE WEBSITE USE "COOKIES"?

Yes, the Website uses cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user’s device to help improve your access to the Website and identify repeat visitors. Cookies can also enable Loot Market to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience. Cookies are not linked to any personally identifiable information.

## HOW DOES LOOT MARKET USE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

Personally identifiable information collected is used primarily for the purpose it is collected (e.g., creating a user account, payment). Loot Market also may use a user’s email address as follows provided that the user grants his/her consent to such additional use: 

  * in internal surveys to obtain feedback on aspects of Loot Market’s business;
  * to notify users of information Loot Market thinks may be of interest to them; and
  * to send communications or promotional materials.

Loot Market may also use personal information collected to contact users in connection with the inappropriate use of the Website.

## DOES LOOT MARKET DISCLOSE MY PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION?

From time to time, Loot Market may disclose your personal information to organizations that perform services for or on behalf of Loot Market, for example to provide customer service, for research, marketing, data processing, and to measure the use of the Website. Loot Market will share with these companies only that personal information which they need to work on our behalf. Some of these service providers may be located in other countries. Your personal information will be provided to these organizations only if they agree to use such information solely for the purpose of providing services to Loot Market, and under the instructions of Loot Market, and with respect to that information, to act in a manner consistent with the relevant principles articulated in this Privacy Policy.

## IS MY PERSONAL INFORMATION SECURE?

The Website has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about Loot Market’s ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, or alteration to you or to any third party. Please review Loot Market’s Terms of Service regarding Loot Market’s liability for any loss, misuse, or alteration of personally identifiable information.

## CAN I UPDATE THE INFORMATION COLLECTED ABOUT ME?

You have the right to correct and update the personal information collected about you through the Website. You can make changes to your personal information at any time by logging into your account. You will need your Steam username and/or trade url in order to access your account.

## WILL YOU NOTIFY ME IN THE EVENT OF CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY?

Loot Market reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy. In the event of a material change in our information collection and handling practices, Loot Market will inform those users who have provided an email address via email. Any changes will apply prospectively only.

## HOW CAN I OPT-OUT FROM RECEIVING EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS?

Loot Market provides you the opportunity to “opt-out” of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes when we ask for this information. For example, if you register for an account but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference during the account creation process. If you opted-in to receive marketing communications but no longer wish to receive communications from us, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each communication.

## LINKS

The Website may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that Loot Market is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. Loot Market encourages users to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Loot Market.

## NOTICE REGARDING CHILDREN

The Website is general audience website and does not direct any of its content specifically at children under 13 years of age. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children’s privacy. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a user is under age 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user’s account.

## INTERNATIONAL USERS

Loot Market is a U.S. company and the Website is hosted in the United States. If you access the Website from the European Union, Asia, or any other region, country, or jurisdiction with privacy laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States privacy laws, please note that, by your continued use of the Website, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer. In addition, you understand that your personal information may be processed in countries (including the United States) where privacy laws may be less stringent than in your country.

## HOW DO I CONTACT LOOT MARKET ABOUT PRIVACY CONCERNS?

If you have any further questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us at help@lootmarket.com.

## REQUIRED DISCLOSURES

Loot Market may disclose personal information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on our site.
